Chris Burton

Mankato, MN

Phone: 712-209-0267 | Email: burton.chris13@gmail.com LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/christopher-burton-aba9651b9

GitHub: https://github.com/Wizzle13

Portfolio: https://wizzle13.github.io/Burton-portfolio

SUMMARY

[Summary section can use either bullet point format or paragraph format to sum up the role you are applying for, accomplishments, relevant past experience, recognitions, and/or roles in projects built]

- **DO NOT** include entire phrases or sentences of this sample in your resume statement.
- **DO NOT** include personal pronouns in your summary (I, me, etc.)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQUery, Bootstrap, Node.js

Applications: VSCode, GitHub, Insomnia

PROJECTS

[Repeat this format for up to 3 projects that are ready to be employer-facing]

Project Name | Link to GitHub | Link to Deployed Project [always write out link addresses]

- Short summary of project (1-2 lines)
- Your core responsibilities in project (1-2 lines)
- Tools / languages used

EXPERIENCE

Final Assembly 2021 – Present AlumaCraft Saint Peter,MN

• Final assembly of aluminum boats.

Production Crew Lead Angie's BoomChickaPop

2017 - 2021

Mankato, MN

Managed crew consisting of 5 Machine operators and 40 production specialists. Assisted employees and resolved issues.

Quality Technician Aerospace Systems

2015 – 2017 Blue Earth, MN

- Wrote First Article Inspection report.
- Final inspection of Completed cables.
- Electrical testing of completed cables

Robot Operator / Assembler 2011 – 2015

Polaris Industries Spirit Lake, IA

- Start and stop operation of Paint Robots.
- · Modifying programs.
- · Checking the quality of painted parts.
- · Assembling Ranger ATV's

EDUCATION

Boot Camp Certificate: University of Minnesota

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Node.js, MySQL, Express, Handelbars.js, and ReactJS.

Wind Energy and Turbine Technology Degree: lowa Lakes Community College, Estherville, IA

A 2 year AAS Degree program covering PLC programming, data acquisition, basic hydraulics, practical wiring and basic turbine maintenance.

Information Technology Degree: Iowa Lakes Community College, Estherville, IA
A 2 year AS Degree program covering Microsoft operating system including Windows
NT and Windows 2000 Operating systems.

Computer Specialist Degree:lowa Lakes Community College, Estherville, IA

A 2 year AS Degree program learning a multitude of programming languages including:

Visual Basic, RPG, Cobal, and Pascal. Along with Problem solving logic.